<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on l3gacy&#39;s b3ta</title>
    <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on l3gacy&#39;s b3ta</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://l3gacy.tk/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://l3gacy.tk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stylegan2, Machine Minds, &amp; Science Communication</title>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/stylegan-machine-minds-and-scicoms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 18:42:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/stylegan-machine-minds-and-scicoms/</guid>
      <description>AI is becoming a more and more important topic in our daily lives, and understanding has stayed about the same. I&amp;rsquo;m here to fix that! One of the very interesting new types of AI are GANs. For this article I&amp;rsquo;ll be talking about one Stylegan2. Stylegan2 is a huge leap in image generation GANs. I know I am a bit behind on this whole shebang, but I just found out that I could run Stylegan2 myself, so I wanted to write about it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>domain name, finaly</title>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/domain-name-finaly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 11:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/domain-name-finaly/</guid>
      <description>So, I finally got l3gacy.tk linked to the github pages! The process was a bit confusing, probably because I&amp;rsquo;ve never done something like this before, but here&amp;rsquo;s the steps I took.
First I got a free domain from freenom.com. Quick tip, if you want one, write out the full domain in the domain search bar instead of just the first part (i.e. example.tk instead of just example). Once I had done that, I signed up for a free cloudflare acount, as they have a better domain-name-manegment-system-thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got this working on github pages!</title>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/got-this-working-on-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/got-this-working-on-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>Well, this was a pain in the butt.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like messing with github actions again, as I hate that thing with a passion. So I was looking through the hexo docs and I found a usefull one-command deploy option. All you have to do is add this little tidbit to your _config.yaml.
 deploy: type: git repo: https://github.com/&amp;lt;username&amp;gt;/&amp;lt;project&amp;gt; # example, https://github.com/l3gacyb3ta/l3gacyb3ta.github.io branch: &amp;lt;whatever branch you use&amp;gt; You also have to install hexo-deployer-git, which is simple, just use this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ethereum &amp; marshy, a new project!</title>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/ethereummarshyanewproject/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 14:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/ethereummarshyanewproject/</guid>
      <description>So a while back I was asked by my dad, &amp;ldquo;What does BitCoin have to do with these computer parts shortages?&amp;quot; Well I knew the basics of the blockchain idea, but I didn&#39;t know the specifics. So after a bit of googling I found out and that was that. Now a few days later I saw a video in my YouTube recommended feed: &amp;ldquo;Programming the blockchain with Ethereum!&amp;rdquo; or something like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>images made by writing bots?</title>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/imagesmadebywritingbots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/imagesmadebywritingbots/</guid>
      <description>~Soo~ today we have something a tad bit more complicated, so first I&#39;ll introduce a few concepts and tools:
1\. Markov chains: From simple.wikipedia.org: &amp;ldquo;A Markov chain is a model of some random process that happens over time. Markov chains are called that because they follow a rule called the Markov property. The Markov property says that whatever happens next in a process only depends on how it is right now (the state).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>better search for windows</title>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/bettersearchforwindows/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 22:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/bettersearchforwindows/</guid>
      <description>A better search for Windows 10, the old one was slow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome!</title>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 01:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s not much here yet! But soon there will be!
To check out the source code for this whole shebang, look for the blog repo in my GitHub! The link is in contacts.
-l3gacy
Update: Old blog posts are now in!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mac OS X .... in a VM‽</title>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/macosxinavm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 22:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/macosxinavm/</guid>
      <description>You may be thinking &amp;ldquo;Why is OS X so intresting?&amp;rdquo; Well this is intresting because it&#39;s running by a VM!
Firstly, you may be asking yourselves &amp;ldquo;Why would you do this?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;What is the point of this?&amp;rdquo;.
The point is, I can, so why not\xe2\x80\xbd
Moving on, how?
First, I installed the &amp;ldquo;Update to Catalina&amp;rdquo; app on my dad&#39;s MacBook Pro. I then followed a guide to transform this app into an .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beach</title>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 21:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/beach/</guid>
      <description>First render: The idea for this was a volleyball scene on a beach island.
This was rendered in TV PAL 16:9.

 Click to view
 DO THIS FOR OTHER VIDEOS
Second render: Textures were reset for this one so I could fix the animation on this.
This was rendered in TV PAL 16:9.

Final render: What I changed here was I added textures to everything,
changed the plane on the bottom to several squares, and added a skybox + water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>motion tracking</title>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/motiontracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 21:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/motiontracking/</guid>
      <description>I tracked approx 20 points in the image.
  I extrapolated the movement of the camera.
  I modeled the window and added the macbook and the drawers.
  Then I exported to a set of 360 images and recombined them into a video.
  That&amp;rsquo;s my youtube channel, btw</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rigging, not the election</title>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/riggingnottheelection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 21:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/riggingnottheelection/</guid>
      <description>V1.0 Walk cycle animation done based on traditonal walk cycle animation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>threadripper ad</title>
      <link>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/threadripperad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 21:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://l3gacy.tk/posts/threadripperad/</guid>
      <description>  First I modeled the Treadripper CPU from AMD.
  Then, I used rigidbody physics to simulate them bouncing away.
  I used Windows Video Editor to sync the audio of the music I stiched together to the AMD text.
  Finally I used Shotcut to edit all videos together.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
